JENNY DEYGIN

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

junikab@gmail.com

0426-112831

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Sydney

Australian Citizen

SKILLS

Languages JavaScript, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, Python.

Libraries React, Express, Bootstrap, Material UI, Cypress.io.

Databases MongoDB, MySQL.

APIs REST, Context.

Extras Git, GitHub, Terminal, MapInfo, mapbox, ArcMap, QGIS, AutoCAD.

I am a junior front-end developer experienced in QA automation using Express, JavaScript, and Cypress.io. Passionate about quality and user experience, I strive to improve my skills and stay up-to-date with industry trends.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Independent | 04/2023 - Present Junior front-end developer

- Developed a diverse portfolio of web applications and sites as part of independent, self-guided projects, demonstrating a strong grasp of front-end development concepts.
- Proficient in a wide range of technologies, including JavaScript, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, and databases such as MongoDB.
- Experienced in using widely used libraries and frameworks like React, Express, Bootstrap, Material UI, and Cypress.io.
- Skilled in API integration and management, utilizing RESTful services and the Context API.

Driva.com | 08/2020 - 01/2021 Junior Automation QA

- Developed and maintained automation scripts using Cypress.io and JavaScript.
- Conducted thorough testing of new features and bug fixes to identify and resolve issues.
- Collaborated with the development team to improve the overall testing process.
- Helped to improve the company's testing coverage and efficiency through the use of automation.

Edukana.com | 05/2019 - 01/2020 Associate Product Owner

- Supporting and leading key initiatives relating to product strategy, specifications and development.
- Engaging with stakeholders to create the product roadmap and onboarding new customers.
- Carrying out user research, competitor analysis and performing UAT.
- Creating wireframes (Balsamiq) for designing new features and functionality for the digital platform.
- Working within an Agile framework.
- Created a wireframe for a blog page that was implemented, with great feedback.

Tel Aviv City Municipality, IT Department | 08/2014 - 09/2016 Product Implementation Manager

- Leading a team of 5 in the implementation of a complex, web-based, city-wide construction licensing and regulation system servicing architects and construction engineers throughout the region.
- Directing system bug prioritisation and resolution using HP ALM.
- Managing Stakeholders and gathering requirements and feature specifications from 200+ users.
- Responsible for training and supporting around 1000+ engineers and architects to use the system.
- Supporting customers via different channels: face to face, phone, email, remotely.
- Identified opportunities for feature improvements, reducing support calls on various issues by 20-40%.

Taldor Computer Systems | 08/2013 - 08/2014 Geographic Information System Technician

- Leading a team in the creation of comprehensive, multi-layer land-use maps.
- Performing graphical data digitisation (AutoCAD), matching to cadastre for land use planning schemes.
- Undertaking data management (SQL database/Excel) as well as data quality assurance of construction rights alphanumeric data.
- Managing database deployment of graphical and alphanumeric end-products (MapGuide/Maestro).

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree In Geography And Human Environment + Management, Archeology sections Tel Aviv University, Israel 2010 - 2014

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

- The Modern React Bootcamp (Udemy), 2023
- The Web Developer Bootcamp 2023 (Udemy), 2023
- JavaScript Basics (Udemy), 2020
- Automated Software Testing with Python (Udemy), 2020
- The Python Bible (Udemy), 2020